<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>The Philosopher's Stone</name>
    <directory>philosophersstone</directory>
    <id>2503994006</id>
    <description>Works well with my [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2504663465]Trinket Stacking+[/url] mod, which give more unique effects to golden trinkets!

The Philosopher's stone is a new active item in the shop item  pool that can be used 3 times. Upon use, it will turn some of the pickups on the ground into their golden variants! This includes coins, keys, bombs, pills, batteries, chests, trinkets, and trollbombs! It will also temporarily freeze enemies in the room into golden statues. Use it wisely, as it can only be used 3 times, and costs 20 coins to buy instead of the usual 15.

Now includes a new Challenge: &quot;Gold Rush!&quot;, which gives you a 6 room charge Philosopher Stone that can be used an infinite amount of times

Note: The item will turn pickups into gold even if you don't have the golden pickup unlocked. For example, hearts will still be converted into golden hearts even if you dont have challenge #21 completed
[h1] Update! [/h1]
[list]
[*]Now has Mod Config Menu support to edit the number of uses 
[*]Fixed the challenge not always giving you the Stone, and made the challenge coop compatible
[/list]
[h1]Item Conversions[/h1]
You can even convert some item pedestals into their golden counterparts. This includes [list]
[*]Iron Bar -&gt;Midas touch
[*]Razor -&gt; Golden razor
[*]Teleport -&gt; Teleport 2.0
[*]Circle of protection -&gt; Dad's ring
[*]Brother bobby -&gt; King baby
[*]Latch key -&gt; Mom's key
[*]There's options -&gt; More options
[*]Options? -&gt; More options
[/list]

[h1]How to edit the number of uses[/h1]
[list]
[*]Option 1: Use Mod Config Menu, and edit the Max Uses under &quot;Philospher Stone&quot;
[*]Option 2: Edit the &quot;MaxUses&quot; in data/philosophersstone/save(saveNumber).dat (the save file will only appear after starting a run and exiting to the menu) The value must be 0,1,2, or 3. Setting it to 0 will give it infinite uses
[/list]
[h1]Compatibility[/h1][list]
[*]Has Extenal Item Descriptions support
[*]Has Mod Config Menu support
[/list]
Known Bugs/Issues:
*Sucking it up with void instantly uses it

Programming by EdinEfin
Item Sprite by PJJLegend</description>
    <version>1.10</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Challenges"/>
</metadata>
